<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Danger Dave</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 12:51:32 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 12:51:32 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Refresh: to make fresh again; reinvigorate or cheer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Several things over the past few days have been very refreshing for me; and in several different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/dingle.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most refreshing moment of all - in a literal sense - was diving in for my first outdoor swim of the year. Some friends and I packed some snacks and biked down Purcell&#39;s Cove Road to a little swimming hole called Williams Lake, which I hadn&#39;t been to before. It&#39;s just past the turnoff to the Dingle (on the opposite side of Purcell&#39;s Cove Rd). The water wasn&#39;t exactly boiling, but it was definitely bearable, and it just felt nice to swim again after about 9 months out of water. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/dive.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Kinda looks like I belly flopped... Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon returning from our trip I can remember, with vivid detail, staring in awe of the old trees covered with young leaves hanging over Quinpool Rd. Just as these trees had been refreshed, so had I. I was reminded of how beautiful our city is, and of how profoundly some colour, life, and vitamin D can impact my state of mind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/lemonade.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;650&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we continued up Quinpool, we came across these adorable little girls selling lemonade for $0.25 to raise money for the IWK and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://convio.cancer.ca/site/TR/Thirdpartyevent/IFE_NS_General_?pg=entry&amp;fr_id=20012#.VWxwzFxVhHw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailblazer 4 Cancer fundraiser&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Tommy put their mixology skills to the test and ordered the signature cocktail &quot;Pink Lightning&quot;, a mix of not only regular lemonade, but pink as well. The girls informed us that after our first purchase, our second cup was free! An eerily similar business model to that of Vogue Optical&#39;s. Lawsuit pending...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also made a quick pit stop at a good-old-fashioned yard sale, where paperback books were selling again for $0.25. Overcome by the awesome nostalgia associated with yard sales and being able to purchase awesome things for a quarter, I picked up Stephen R. Covey&#39;s
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/36072.The_7_Habits_of_Highly_Effective_People&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;7 Habits of Highly Effective People.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/theboys.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Ho-Jin, Tommy and I before heading down to the lake&lt;br&gt;Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I can&#39;t forget our awesome Lawn Summer Nights Team, who participated in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://cysticfibrosis.ca/greatstrides/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carstar Great Strides Walk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to support Cystic Fibrosis research and to spread awareness for Lawn Summer Nights. It was great for our team to have a chance to speak with some families and individuals directly impacted by Cystic Fibrosis. It helped us gain some valuable perspective and reminded us again why Lawn Summer Nights exists and the positive impact that events like this have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/team.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; SQUAD. &lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halifax Lawn Summer Nights has been nominated for a Maritime Philanthropy Award and will be throwing its official &quot;Lawnch Party&quot; at the Scanway Patio on June 12th from 6-8pm! All attendees must RSVP to halifax@lawnsummernights.com. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
















		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/06/01/swim-and-lemonade.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/06/01/swim-and-lemonade.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just What I needed</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s been ten days since my last post. Between a mix of spring courses at SMU, work, and some general anxiety, I&#39;d found myself in a bit of a rut the past few days. Having recognized that I was slipping, I tried waking up at 5am, in an attempt to get ahead and lay out my week, but found myself distracted and unable to give my full attention to any one of my competing priorities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I know it sounds cliché, but I figured some time outside with friends might be all I needed to get myself back on track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/turret.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a quick trip out to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?q=duncan%27s+cove&amp;espv=2&amp;biw=1680&amp;bih=843&amp;source=lnms&amp;tbm=isch&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=g3JjVcO7NOPLsASPyICwBQ&amp;ved=0CAcQ_AUoAg&amp;dpr=2&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Duncan&#39;s Cove Nature Reserve&lt;/a&gt;(photos below), I found myself both mentally and physically refreshed. We followed up the hike with an awesome BBQ, and we were even given free burgers at Sobeys! Yeah, and then I got food poisoning... &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/dead.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Nothing like waking up wearing a hoodie and sweatpants, covered in cold sweat, dehydrated, and confused all at the same time! And yes, that is me in that photo.&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m feeling better now, and with improving weather and spring courses coming to an end soon enough, I am super excited to start checking off some of my summer to-do&#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a very proud moment earlier this week. Ho-Jin had just come home from sorting out his visa situation and ever-so-eloquently described the experience as &quot;a shit show&quot;. You don&#39;t learn that one at ESL school!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check out some photos from the hike down below, but before that, I&#39;ll throw down a few links to some cool stuff I&#39;ve stumbled upon recently. Check &#39;em out!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/MoviePosterPorn/top/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Reddit Movie Poster Porn:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; No this is not actually porn... It&#39;s a list of all the best fan-made movie posters. In my opinion, most of them are way better than the originals!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickchart.com/Charts.aspx?genre=Anime&amp;perpage=100&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt; - 100 Best Anime Movies of All Time:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; This is awesome. If you haven&#39;t tried watching anime movies before, I highly recommend trying a few of these out. I just watched &lt;em&gt;My Neighbor Totoro&lt;/em&gt; for the first time, and felt like I was a kid again. If you&#39;re looking for something more serious, try &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oP2Pt6m3yKU&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;em&gt;Ghost in the Shell.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Apparently it served as inspiration in the creation of &lt;em&gt;The Matrix.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icheckmovies.com/lists/reddit+top+250/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Reddit&#39;s Top 250 Movies - Courtesy of iCheck Movies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; I&#39;ve been using this list for a while now and it is MONEY. I find, when browsing IMDB or Rotten Tomatoes, I tend to agree with ratings and lists maybe 65% of the time. Obviously this is very subjective, but I&#39;ve found this movie list to be the best I&#39;ve come across for sure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://agenda.weforum.org/2015/05/what-13-successful-leaders-read-every-morning/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Reading/Morning Routines of 13 Successful Leaders:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; I found this list interesting and motivating. Makes me want to do some more magazine reading. There are some interesting links within this article as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt; Hike Photos! &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/clear2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/selfie.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/wave.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/goat.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;This stump looked just like a goat to me^^^&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/clear.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/look.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/climb.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;






		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/25/hike-to-duncans.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/25/hike-to-duncans.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Value of Writing Things Down &lt;br&gt;(a non-scientific angle)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Every time you have a cool idea, a profound thought, or see something you want to remember, write it down! It may seem daunting at first, but once you make it a priority to right down anything and everything that may be of use to you, you will soon reap the benefits, of which there are plenty.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/writing.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may have noticed that I have re-designed my blog a little bit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&#39;re not on a phone, try clicking the above image^^^&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Boom.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h6&gt;(shoutout to Dawson Reid for the coding help)&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, back to business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since childhood, I&#39;ve been quite forgetful. Generally, with trivial things mind you. I&#39;d get to the hockey rink, only to find out I forgot my skates, I&#39;d show up to class without my field trip permission slip, or even take the bus home without my backpack. In the image below, you will see a 100% genuine screenshot of a few of my recent iPhone alarms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/ifen.png&quot; height=&quot;230&quot; width=&quot;230&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt; That&#39;s right... &quot;7:49&quot;, &quot;8:36&quot; &amp; &quot;8:37&quot;. You might have noticed, &quot;call g rents&quot;, in there as well. Just a simple reminder to call my grandparents because it wass important to me, and I didn&#39;t want to forget to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;If it&#39;s so important to you, why do you need an alarm to remember it?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love my grandparents, but that doesn&#39;t mean I can&#39;t get distracted by one of the 10,000 other things I think about on a day-to-day basis. I&#39;m 22 years old. I&#39;m in classes, I work, I&#39;ve made a commitment to pretend I know anything about anything on this blog, and on occasion I waste anywhere from 5 to 35 minutes imagining what I would do if I went back in time, to when I was 7 years old, knowing everything I know now. Just because something is important to me, doesn&#39;t mean it won&#39;t slip my mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt; There’s a ridiculous amount of hard science, proving that writing any given thing down increases your chances of remembering it, even if you never look at it again. Instead of scraping the internet for some second-hand science, I&#39;ll try to describe the benefits of writing things down, from my own experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Here is a list of ways you can benefit, by being proactive in writing things down:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#1 - You&#39;re able to &quot;prioritize your priorities&quot;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; If you make a point of writing down all of the things you need/want to get done, you can actually sort them in order of importance. By tackling my goals individually, and in order of urgency/importance, I find I&#39;m able to work a lot more efficiently. You can also reduce the weight of all your to-do&#39;s, by eliminating the ones you simply don&#39;t have time for. Now that you&#39;ve eliminated them, these thoughts no longer linger, clouding your mind and wasting your limited brain power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;#2 - You can constantly refine your processes. And it&#39;s fun!!!.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; Have you ever found and read some of your old schoolwork? It&#39;s interesting to see how you&#39;ve grown over the years. Perhaps even more interesting, is seeing how much your thoughts and mindset can change in a much smaller timeframe. Everytime you look back on your notes, you&#39;re in at least a slightly different mindset than when you initially wrote them down. Each time you look back, you offer a different perspective on your own ideas. That&#39;s how the refining process works! And it&#39;s exciting to feel yourself learning and growing!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;#3 - You can enhance the experience you get from reading a book.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; Even if you&#39;re just reading for leisure, it can&#39;t hurt to learn something! Try using a blank, stiff piece of paper as a bookmark, and writing down each word you cannot provide a clear definition for. You can either look the words up as you go, or take some time every few days to look them all up at once. Although I prefer the feel of a real book, I often use my tablet for harder reads, as I can easily retrieve a word&#39;s definition and highlight sections of the book that I might like to review.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/img_1059.png&quot; height=&quot;230&quot; width=&quot;230&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt; &lt;h6&gt;please excuse my terrible hand-writing&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#4 - It can really help you get to know yourself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; As cliché as it sounds, I&#39;ve discovered that this is an excellent way to better understand myself, my thoughts and my priorities. Taking the time to sit down alone and reflect on your own thoughts and ideas in a systematic fashion can seem like a strange concept at first, but it is in itself, a process that you continue to refine in order to understand both yourself and your environment on a more intimate level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

	&lt;br&gt;

Set goals, write them down, and list them in order of importance. 5 Months ago I had a list of goals, and at the top of that list was &quot;learn to code to make a blog&quot;. And here we are.

&lt;/p&gt;
















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/12/6--writing-things-down.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/12/6--writing-things-down.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Things in Halifax That You Probably Haven&#39;t Tried</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Halifax is not a huge city by any means. Many people here feel as though they&#39;ve seen and done it all. If you count yourself among those who feel that way, I bet you&#39;re wrong!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/lawnsum.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it&#39;s food, drink, music, places to explore, or maybe an event you&#39;ve never been too, I can guarantee that there is still something new and awesome for you to try here in Halifax.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;In no particular order, here is a list of some of my favourite things you may not have already tried:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#1 Spicy Chili Chicken – The Great Wall Chinese: &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If KFC’s Popcorn Chicken and Sriracha Chili Sauce made a baby, you’d get The Great Wall’s Spicy Chili Chicken on their traditional menu. One of the most flavourful foods I’ve ever eaten. Try it with a bowl of rice and chopsticks, but be careful not to chomp on one of the full chili peppers mixed in with the chicken.  Unless you’re just raw like that, I guess.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
For a quicker and cheaper (but still delicious) version, try the Seoul Chicken at Korean Garden Express in Scotia Square!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#2 Lawn Summer Nights – St. Mary’s Lawn Bowls Club:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last summer, St. Mary’s Lawn Bowls Club hosted Halifax’s very first Lawn Summer Nights Lawn Bowling Tournament in an effort to raise money and awareness in order to help those living with Cystic Fibrosis in Canada. Last year’s events were a huge success, with the Halifax chapter contributing $25,000 to a nationwide $1,000,000 raised by Lawn Summer Nights since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/lawnsum2.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights was originally inspired by a courageous woman named Eva Markvoort, who spent her life with Cystic Fibrosis and made it her personal mission to find a cure for the disease. For more info on Eva’s story, and the history of Lawn Summer Nights, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://lawnsummernights.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;Lawnsummernights.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights was one of the most, if not the most, exciting part of my 2014 summer. Teams of four dressed up in vintage attire, competed over the span of four consecutive Thursday nights, and enjoyed food, drinks, live music, and some powerful words from leaders in our community living with Cystic Fibrosis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights is an event powered by passionate individuals from Halifax’s young professional community, looking to raise money for a great cause, which has seen several major advances over the past decade. Registration opens at noon on Monday, May 11th and the cost is $400 per team. If you are interested in attending, have your team ready to register on Monday! Toronto, Victoria and Vancouver’s events sold out in the first 3 minutes! This years events will take place on Thursday, July 2nd, 9th, 16th, and 23, with and 30th as a rain date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn.png&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn.png&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#3 Beef Jerky - Lion &amp; Bright Café: &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thick slices, not too dry and super tasty. I’ve probably had Lion and Bright’s beef jerky about 10 times now.  I’m always convincing strangers to try it, and I might be the only person to try to order it for breakfast. Don’t Spend $5 on gas station jerky when you can get the real deal at Lion and Bright on Agricola for the same price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;h4&gt;#4 My Father’s Bowtie Collection – Biscuit General Store:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This past year, in lieu of the standard black or blue tie, at StFX’s famous X-Ring Ceremony, about 95% of the guys were rocking bowties. The man behind this was recent StFX graduate and Entrepreneur, Demetrius Ferguson. Demetrius started selling his bowties in November of 2014, one week before X-Ring. My Father’s Bowtie Collection provides a unique selection of patterns and fabrics with a vintage twist. Handcrafted in Prince Edward Island, this is a true artisan product and, at only $35, makes for a fantastic gift!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/ties.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Father’s Bowtie Collection is now available in Halifax at Biscuit General Store on Argyle Street. Check out some more ties on MFC&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/mfc_bowties/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;instagram page!&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/aj.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;h4&gt;#5 Graphic Novels at The Halifax Central Library:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just finished Frank Miller’s &lt;em&gt;Batman: The Dark Knight Returns&lt;/em&gt;, duuuude… 
I can’t believe it has taken me this long to get into graphic novels. The Halifax Central Library has shelves full of these things. I also hear that the Keshen Goodman Library in Clayton Park has an even better collection. If you’re thinking, “Pfft, I don’t have time to read comics”, this 224 pager only took me 4-5 hours (and I’m not a fast reader). If you watch “The Big Bang Theory”, I would suggest just dropping that bad habit in order to make more time. That show is terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I scooped these ones, in the image below, from The Halifax Central Library today. You can also see that I&#39;ve downloaded some comics to read on my tablet. Super easy to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/comics.png&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, keep in mind that not all comics and graphic novels are about superheroes.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out a list of some other awesome graphic novels &lt;a href=&quot;https://forbiddenplanet.com/log/recommendations/50-best-best-graphic-novels/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here!&lt;/a&gt; (have a look at #1)&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Get out and give these a try!&lt;/h4&gt;











	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/08/6-things-halifax.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/08/6-things-halifax.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bike Ride to york Redoubt</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It was 20 degrees Celsius, it took several hours, there was still snow, I got a really bad sunburn, it was worth it. &lt;a href=&quot;http://dangerdave.ninja/media/&quot;&gt;Check out the photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Ho-Jin and I took our new bikes down Purcell’s Cove Road to the York Redoubt National Historic Site. It did not disappoint! Along the way were plenty of awesome spots to stop and admire Halifax and Dartmouth all the way down to Eastern Passage over the water. The trip, which travels down Purcell’s Cove Road and returns via Herring Cove Road, is about 30-35km’s altogether. It is riddled with huge hills, which are insanely fun to cruise down, but not so much to drive up… The run can be challenging if you’re not in awesome shape (I am not), but if you walk your bike up some of the steeper hills, that will save you a lot of energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have a bike, I highly recommend buying one! I paid $200 for a decent road bike on Kijiji and paid about $100 in tune-ups to have it running great. With a bike, the city feels a lot smaller and you can really “get two birds stoned at once” by getting your exercise in while commuting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are great bike lanes for most of the ride, and the areas without bike lanes don’t really need them, seeing as traffic really dies down as you travel farther out of town. At the end of Purcell’s Cove Road is the Pavia Gallery - Espresso Bar and Café. As we pulled up to the café, promising food and beer, I taught Ho-Jin a new English expression, “the light at the end of the tunnel”. You’ll find Ho-Jin seeing the light in the first &lt;a href=&quot;http://dangerdave.ninja/media/&quot;&gt;photo&lt;/a&gt;. The ride back on the Herring Cove Road is refreshingly flat so, unless your limbs are falling off, no need to worry about the ride back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;York Redoubt was awesome, and had me asking myself how I had never been there before. That’s one of the best things about showing Ho-Jin around Nova Scotia; I’m finding myself constantly blown away by some of the places and sights that, as a Halifax native, I have taken for granted for far too long. For those of you who haven’t seen the site, a quick Google search will tell you that York Redoubt is “a redoubt situated on a bluff”. NICE! I’ve saved 92% of you the trouble of “Googling” the word redoubt. Merriam Webster online says that a redoubt is “a small usually temporary enclosed defensive work”. Here is a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pc.gc.ca/eng/lhn-nhs/ns/york/index.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; to the website for anyone interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I’m at it, I’m going to Google “bluff” as well! According to Dictionary.com, a bluff is “a cliff, headland, or hill with a broad, steep face”. For me, “bluff” was one of those words I’ve heard and vaguely understood many times, without &lt;em&gt;fully&lt;/em&gt; understanding what it meant. That’s another thing that has been really interesting, while helping Ho-Jin learn English. It is so easy to nod your head yes when someone asks if you know what a word or expression means. You might be surprised though, when asked to explain the meaning of a seemingly simply word or expression, how difficult it can be to explain to a person who has never heard it before. My brother and I had a hard time explaining the verb “warrant”. We ended up using “justify” to explain it, but the two are not exactly synonymous. Not easy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On another note, for the last few months I’ve been telling myself “I need to get away, I want to experience other places, other cultures”. I’ve felt as though I am trapped and that there is nothing left for me in Nova Scotia. How arrogant, how terribly wrong I have been about that. Although I would still love to travel, I’ve found excitement in exploring my own city and province, and in learning about Korean culture from Ho-Jin. The improving weather should help as well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently created an account on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.couchsurfing.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Couchsurfing.com&lt;/a&gt;, and will be hosting two girls from Germany for a few nights in the middle of May. I’m really looking forward to showing them around!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My media page is pretty sloppy at the moment, so I’ve got some coding to do.  I’m also in class right now, so I should probably be listening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Til next time!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/04/trip-to-yorkredoubt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/04/trip-to-yorkredoubt.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Blog Entry &amp; The Power of a Random Compliment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My very first blog post, featuring an introductory video and a cheesy story about the power of a small compliment. 
 &lt;strong&gt;Please watch this video before reading!!!&lt;/strong&gt;     »»     &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6BHxqogqMoc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ho-Jin and Dave Intros&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few months back, I was walking down Spring Garden Road in Halifax, when I saw someone wearing a nice pair of boots. I thought to myself, “Hm, I like those boots”, so I told him, “I like those boots”. He was a bit startled when I said it, and I asked him where he had bought them. He told me that he’d bought them in Korea. After asking a few more questions, I learned that he was from South Korea, he hadn’t yet seen the city, nor had he met any friends.  Without really thinking about it, I just asked “want a friend?”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though he seemed a little surprised, Ho-Jin was happy to take my number and I asked him to text me when he wanted to meet up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then Ho-Jin and I have become great friends. He just finished up at the ECSL School on Barrington St. in Halifax, and I will now be acting as Ho-Jin’s English tutor. Had I kept the small compliment to myself, we never would have met, and both would have missed out on a great friendship and learning experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have something nice to say, SAY IT! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which, this blog was inspired by someone a lot smarter and cooler than myself! Her name is Mel Hattie, and you can check out her work at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.melhattie.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MelHattie.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/01/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/01/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
