<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Danger Dave</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 18:22:16 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 18:22:16 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>6 Things in Halifax That You Probably Haven&#39;t Tried</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Halifax is not a huge city by any means. Many people here feel as though they&#39;ve seen and done it all. If you count yourself among those who feel that way, I bet you&#39;re wrong!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/lawnsum.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;700&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it&#39;s food, drink, music, places to explore, or maybe an event you&#39;ve never been too, I can guarantee that there is still something new and awesome for you to try here in Halifax.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;In no particular order, here is a list of some of my favourite things you may not have already tried:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#1 Spicy Chili Chicken – The Great Wall Chinese: &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If KFC’s Popcorn Chicken and Sriracha Chili Sauce made a baby, you’d get The Great Wall’s Spicy Chili Chicken on their traditional menu. One of the most flavourful foods I’ve ever eaten. Try it with a bowl of rice and chopsticks, but be careful not to chomp on one of the full chili peppers mixed in with the chicken.  Unless you’re just raw like that, I guess.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
For a quicker and cheaper (but still delicious) version, try the Seoul Chicken at Korean Garden Express in Scotia Square!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#2 Lawn Summer Nights – St. Mary’s Lawn Bowls Club:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last summer, St. Mary’s Lawn Bowls Club hosted Halifax’s very first Lawn Summer Nights Lawn Bowling Tournament in an effort to raise money and awareness in order to help those living with Cystic Fibrosis in Canada. Last year’s events were a huge success, with the Halifax chapter contributing $25,000 to a nationwide $1,000,000 raised by Lawn Summer Nights since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center data-action=&quot;zoom&quot; &quot; src=&quot;/img/lawnsum2.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;700&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights was originally inspired by a courageous woman named Eva Markvoort, who spent her life with Cystic Fibrosis and made it her personal mission to find a cure for the disease. For more info on Eva’s story, and the history of Lawn Summer Nights, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://lawnsummernights.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lawnsummernights.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights was one of the most, if not the most, exciting part of my 2014 summer. Teams of four dressed up in vintage attire, competed over the span of four consecutive Thursday nights, and enjoyed food, drinks, live music, and some powerful words from leaders in our community living with Cystic Fibrosis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights is an event powered by passionate individuals from Halifax’s young professional community, looking to raise money for a great cause, which has seen several major advances over the past decade. Registration opens at noon on Monday, May 11th and the cost is $400 per team. If you are interested in attending, have your team ready to register on Monday! Toronto, Victoria and Vancouver’s events sold out in the first 3 minutes! This years events will take place on Thursday, July 2nd, 9th, 16th, and 23, with and 30th as a rain date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn.png&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#3 Beef Jerky - Lion &amp; Bright Café: &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thick slices, not too dry and super tasty. I’ve probably had Lion and Bright’s beef jerky about 10 times now.  I’m always convincing strangers to try it, and I might be the only person to try to order it for breakfast. Don’t Spend $5 on gas station jerky when you can get the real deal at Lion and Bright on Agricola for the same price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;h4&gt;#4 My Father’s Bowtie Collection – Biscuit General Store:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This past year, in lieu of the standard black or blue tie, at StFX’s famous X-Ring Ceremony, about 95% of the guys were rocking bowties. The man behind this was recent StFX graduate and Entrepreneur, Demetrius Ferguson. Demetrius started selling his bowties in November of 2014, one week before X-Ring. My Father’s Bowtie Collection provides a unique selection of patterns and fabrics with a vintage twist. Handcrafted in Prince Edward Island, this is a true artisan product and, at only $35, makes for a fantastic gift!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/ties.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Father’s Bowtie Collection is now available in Halifax at Biscuit General Store on Argyle Street. Check out some more ties on MFC&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/mfc_bowties/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;instagram page!&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/aj.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;h4&gt;#5 Graphic Novels at The Halifax Central Library:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just finished Frank Miller’s &lt;em&gt;Batman: The Dark Knight Returns&lt;/em&gt;, duuuude… 
I can’t believe it has taken me this long to get into graphic novels. The Halifax Central Library has shelves full of these things. I also hear that the Keshen Goodman Library in Clayton Park has an even better collection. If you’re thinking, “Pfft, I don’t have time to read comics”, this 224 pager only took me 4-5 hours (and I’m not a fast reader). If you watch “The Big Bang Theory”, I would suggest just dropping that bad habit in order to make more time. That show is terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I scooped these ones, in the image below, from The Halifax Central Library today. You can also see that I&#39;ve downloaded some comics to read on my tablet. Super easy to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/comics.png&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;700&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, keep in mind that not all comics and graphic novels are about superheroes.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out a list of some other awesome graphic novels &lt;a href=&quot;https://forbiddenplanet.com/log/recommendations/50-best-best-graphic-novels/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here!&lt;/a&gt; (have a look at #1)&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Get out and give these a try!&lt;/h4&gt;











	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/08/6-things-halifax.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/08/6-things-halifax.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bike Ride to york Redoubt</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It was 20 degrees Celsius, it took several hours, there was still snow, I got a really bad sunburn, it was worth it. &lt;a href=&quot;http://dangerdave.ninja/media/&quot;&gt;Check out the photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Ho-Jin and I took our new bikes down Purcell’s Cove Road to the York Redoubt National Historic Site. It did not disappoint! Along the way were plenty of awesome spots to stop and admire Halifax and Dartmouth all the way down to Eastern Passage over the water. The trip, which travels down Purcell’s Cove Road and returns via Herring Cove Road, is about 30-35km’s altogether. It is riddled with huge hills, which are insanely fun to cruise down, but not so much to drive up… The run can be challenging if you’re not in awesome shape (I am not), but if you walk your bike up some of the steeper hills, that will save you a lot of energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have a bike, I highly recommend buying one! I paid $200 for a decent road bike on Kijiji and paid about $100 in tune-ups to have it running great. With a bike, the city feels a lot smaller and you can really “get two birds stoned at once” by getting your exercise in while commuting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are great bike lanes for most of the ride, and the areas without bike lanes don’t really need them, seeing as traffic really dies down as you travel farther out of town. At the end of Purcell’s Cove Road is the Pavia Gallery - Espresso Bar and Café. As we pulled up to the café, promising food and beer, I taught Ho-Jin a new English expression, “the light at the end of the tunnel”. You’ll find Ho-Jin seeing the light in the first &lt;a href=&quot;http://dangerdave.ninja/media/&quot;&gt;photo&lt;/a&gt;. The ride back on the Herring Cove Road is refreshingly flat so, unless your limbs are falling off, no need to worry about the ride back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;York Redoubt was awesome, and had me asking myself how I had never been there before. That’s one of the best things about showing Ho-Jin around Nova Scotia; I’m finding myself constantly blown away by some of the places and sights that, as a Halifax native, I have taken for granted for far too long. For those of you who haven’t seen the site, a quick Google search will tell you that York Redoubt is “a redoubt situated on a bluff”. NICE! I’ve saved 92% of you the trouble of “Googling” the word redoubt. Merriam Webster online says that a redoubt is “a small usually temporary enclosed defensive work”. Here is a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pc.gc.ca/eng/lhn-nhs/ns/york/index.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; to the website for anyone interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I’m at it, I’m going to Google “bluff” as well! According to Dictionary.com, a bluff is “a cliff, headland, or hill with a broad, steep face”. For me, “bluff” was one of those words I’ve heard and vaguely understood many times, without &lt;em&gt;fully&lt;/em&gt; understanding what it meant. That’s another thing that has been really interesting, while helping Ho-Jin learn English. It is so easy to nod your head yes when someone asks if you know what a word or expression means. You might be surprised though, when asked to explain the meaning of a seemingly simply word or expression, how difficult it can be to explain to a person who has never heard it before. My brother and I had a hard time explaining the verb “warrant”. We ended up using “justify” to explain it, but the two are not exactly synonymous. Not easy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On another note, for the last few months I’ve been telling myself “I need to get away, I want to experience other places, other cultures”. I’ve felt as though I am trapped and that there is nothing left for me in Nova Scotia. How arrogant, how terribly wrong I have been about that. Although I would still love to travel, I’ve found excitement in exploring my own city and province, and in learning about Korean culture from Ho-Jin. The improving weather should help as well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently created an account on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.couchsurfing.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Couchsurfing.com&lt;/a&gt;, and will be hosting two girls from Germany for a few nights in the middle of May. I’m really looking forward to showing them around!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My media page is pretty sloppy at the moment, so I’ve got some coding to do.  I’m also in class right now, so I should probably be listening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Til next time!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/04/trip-to-yorkredoubt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/04/trip-to-yorkredoubt.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Blog Entry &amp; The Power of a Random Compliment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My very first blog post, featuring an introductory video and a cheesy story about the power of a small compliment. 
 &lt;strong&gt;Please watch this video before reading!!!&lt;/strong&gt;     »»     &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6BHxqogqMoc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ho-Jin and Dave Intros&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few months back, I was walking down Spring Garden Road in Halifax, when I saw someone wearing a nice pair of boots. I thought to myself, “Hm, I like those boots”, so I told him, “I like those boots”. He was a bit startled when I said it, and I asked him where he had bought them. He told me that he’d bought them in Korea. After asking a few more questions, I learned that he was from South Korea, he hadn’t yet seen the city, nor had he met any friends.  Without really thinking about it, I just asked “want a friend?”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though he seemed a little surprised, Ho-Jin was happy to take my number and I asked him to text me when he wanted to meet up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then Ho-Jin and I have become great friends. He just finished up at the ECSL School on Barrington St. in Halifax, and I will now be acting as Ho-Jin’s English tutor. Had I kept the small compliment to myself, we never would have met, and both would have missed out on a great friendship and learning experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have something nice to say, SAY IT! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which, this blog was inspired by someone a lot smarter and cooler than myself! Her name is Mel Hattie, and you can check out her work at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.melhattie.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MelHattie.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/01/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2015/05/01/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
