<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dave Culligan</title>
    <description>Blog website, following the life and adventures of David Culligan. 
</description>
    <link>http://daveculligan.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://daveculligan.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 16:46:52 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 16:46:52 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Filming at Falck and Morning Run Video</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, Ho-Jin and I took the ferry and visited my friend Ben at Falck Safety Services in Dartmouth to get some footage for an ad I&#39;m helping with. I had planned on doing a full video blog yesterday morning, but ran into some issues, so I&#39;ve just got a video of my morning run. I also have some footage from Falck. Please note, it is not an ad for Falck Safety Services, but simply something we cut up as a preliminary test. Enjoy!  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Here is my morning run video&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/26khFMsQ39U&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;And here is what we put together from the falck footage&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;The very last clip, I caught on my way home, while waiting for the ferry.&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LOcb_ThTsvs&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When starting this blog, I had no idea where I wanted to go with it, and I&#39;m still not really sure. That being said, it has been a lot of fun and all the positive feedback means a lot to me. HoJin and I were asked to do an interview on CBC Radio&#39;s &lt;em&gt;Information Morning&lt;/em&gt; and we spoke about how we met, and our summer plans. I think it went really well, and Ho-Jin really impressed me with his confidence during the interview. I&#39;m not sure if I&#39;m allowed to share the recording, but if I can, I will post it as soon as I hear back!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day the interview aired was my blog&#39;s busiest day for web traffic, and I even received some emails from strangers, saying very nice things. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of small projects on the go right now, looking forward to making some more videos, and seriously considering supplementing/replacing some written posts, with video blogs (vlogs).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Here are some more photos from Monday&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/falck.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/falck2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/cross.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/snail.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;






















		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/23/Falck-and-Run.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/23/Falck-and-Run.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Single Morning Project</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am finally finished my spring courses, and I am liberated for the summer! All through exams, I kept telling myself that if I weren&#39;t studying, I&#39;d be out doing cool stuff and making the most of my time. Now that they&#39;re over, I promised myself that I would do just that. This morning I challenged myself to film, edit, post, and blog about a video before 10:00am. Check it out!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/grDk-n4VKQk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Admittedly, this will be posted at about 10:30am, but I still had an awesome morning and learned a few things! I bought a tripod off Kijiji, and I&#39;ve been doing some reading about getting the most out of your iPhone camera. I even found out that one of the best films at Sundance was filmed on an iPhone 5. I thought that was super cool. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you want to read the article, click &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theverge.com/2015/1/28/7925023/sundance-film-festival-2015-tangerine-iphone-5s&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; HERE!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And here is a whole website dedicated to iPhone photography! - &lt;a href=&quot;http://iphonephotographyschool.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; iPhone Photography School&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The water at Chocolate Lake was actually insanely warm (like bathwater warm). I&#39;ll definitely be going back for some more morning dips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m so excited to do more biking, hiking, camping, filming, editing, reading, writing, coding and other stuffing now that school is done. Woo!&lt;/p&gt;


























		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/19/Morning-Video.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/19/Morning-Video.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Motivation For Your Monday</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;With today being Monday, and with final exams for spring courses this week, I know I could use some extra motivation/inspiration. For anyone else needing a little push, here are a few links that are certain to do the trick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/melville.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wanderers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt; A short film by erik wernquist&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This four-minute short film by Erik Wernquist, narrated by some old &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carl_Sagan&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Carl Sagan &lt;/a&gt; recordings, is certain to give you chills. The film features some mind-blowing CGI, depicting human expansion out into new worlds, as well as an equally mind-blowing score and some riveting quotes from Dr. Sagan, regarding human existence and our inherent craving for exploration. My favourite quote, &quot;I am tormented with an everlasting itch for things remote, I love to sail forbidden seas&quot;, from Herman Melville&#39;s &lt;em&gt;Moby Dick.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this film does not inspire you, I&#39;m almost certain that nothing will...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410px&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q6goNzXrmFs&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Make It Count&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt; A Nike ad by Casey Neistat&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, my brother told me about a New York-based film director/producer named Casey Neistat. The guy is entertaining, creative, and super ambitious. He&#39;s inspired &lt;em&gt;himself&lt;/em&gt; by tattooing the phrases &quot;work harder&quot; and &quot;do more&quot; on his arms, in almost disturbingly simple fonts. Hopefully he can inspire you too! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410px&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WxfZkMm3wcg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dream&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt; A motivational video by Mateusz M&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you&#39;re one of the 21 million people, who have already watched this video. If you are, watch it again. Maybe I&#39;m just seduced by awesome music tracks, but I don&#39;t think that&#39;s the case. Every time I listen to this, I feel like I&#39;m ready to run through walls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410px&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/g-jwWYX7Jlo&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Now Go do stuff!!!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

























		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/15/Motivation-Monday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/15/Motivation-Monday.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Solo Camping Trip To Bluff WIlderness Trail</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few days ago, I decided that I wanted to go on a solo biking/hiking/camping run. I decided to stay relatively close to home, and chose the Bluff Wilderness Trail in Timberlea, Nova Scotia as my destination. I picked up a $15 iPhone tripod to help me capture the trip, and biked out from Halifax. I made a short video, including of some of my biking footage and a time lapse of me setting up the tent and fire as the sun sets. Check it out!  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4APURUB-5WA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As awesome as it is to camp with friends, camping alone was such a refreshing experience for me. All I had to listen to were my own thoughts, birds, crickets, and the small streams of water flowing beneath my feet. My original plan was to get lots of reading done, but once I was out there staring at the fire and listening to its crackle, I didn&#39;t want to do anything else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff.png&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For anyone who hasn&#39;t hiked the Bluff Wilderness Trail, you need to get out there! It&#39;s packed with beautiful views, perfect camping spots, and a clean, swimmable lake. I also had not been on the Rails to Trails in Timberlea for quite a long time. Since then, it has improved a lot. You can now drive along a paved bike path all the way from Timberlea to the Joseph Howe Drive entrance to the Ashburn Golf Course in Halifax. It&#39;s also quite a scenic and enjoyable ride, especially if the sun is out!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m looking forward to my next trip to the Bluff Wilderness Trail, and hiking a lot farther out with some comrades!&lt;hr&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt; I&#39;ve attached a few more photos from my trip below! &lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff/bluff - 1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff/bluff - 4.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff/bluff - 3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff/bluff - 7.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff/bluff - 2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff/bluff - 5.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bluff/bluff - 6.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;




















		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/09/Bluff-Nature-Trail.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/09/Bluff-Nature-Trail.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Aiming To Be A Killer Grandparent Is An Awesome Life Goal</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;What motivates you? If you&#39;re not able to answer that question right away, a great place to start might be to live in pursuit of becoming the best grandparent you can possibly be. There are so many reasons why this mantra should lead one to live an exciting, meaningful, and fulfilling life that they can look back on fondly and proudly. Here is a short list of a few of those reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/badgrandpa.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Photo Courtesy Paramount Pictures &lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;THE STORIES &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/u&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;(Bonus Points If They’re Well-Documented)&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having some &lt;strong&gt;AWESOME STORIES&lt;/strong&gt; is crucial, if you want to be a killer Grandma or Grandpa (or both? Because gender stuff! You can be a Grand-Dragon for all I care, just be an awesome Grand-Dragon!).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you spend your life doing crazy, wonderful, interesting things, and creating beautiful stories, obviously you’re going to enjoy yourself in the process. Perhaps the best part though, even once you’re old, tired, and no longer physically able to jump off waterfalls, run from bulls, or rage at music festivals, you can hopefully relive these stories by telling them to your grandchildren at an inappropriate age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/davegrand.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;350&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AND, if you’ve got written, witness, photo, or – in the best possible case – video evidence of these spectacular events, your grandchildren will worship you. You’ll also have cool stuff to show off to your golf buddies in Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need some help or inspiration with the video evidence part, check out my friend Mat Barkley and his awesome team at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.badfunmedia.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; BADFUNMEDIA.COM.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Motivation to not Destroy the Earth &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter how many incredible stories you have about the glory days, your grandchildren will have an awfully hard time enjoying those stories if they’re born into a post-apocalyptic nightmare, with no food and no more polar bears. They will be especially pissed off if they know it’s your fault, because you couldn’t be bothered to recycle, drove a Hummer, and fracked the whole planet up for everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who choose to turn a blind eye, or who simply don’t care about future generations, have fun listening to this!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/8MZlMMvXz1A&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Extra Incentive to Maintain Your Integrity&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someday, I think it’s safe to say that most of us hope to have grandchildren of our own, and hope that we’ll have given them reason to be proud of us and what we’ve done with our lives. A surefire way to screw that up would be to treat everyone around you like dirt, and develop a reputation as a classless jerk. The last thing you want is for your grandkids to grow up and find out that you were an ass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, nobody is perfect. If you’re like me, and you’ve made your share of mistakes, it might be a good idea to swallow your pride and apologize directly for them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;













		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/06/Be-A-Killer-Grandparent.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/06/Be-A-Killer-Grandparent.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Things I Wish I Knew Before Going to University </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt; I firmly believe that hindsight is a dreadful waste of time and energy. Not to mention the strain in puts on your mental health. Every second spent thinking about what we could have or should have done in the past, is better spent focusing on what is actually within our control – &lt;strong&gt;NOW&lt;/strong&gt; .  That being said, there are more than a few things I wish I had known while choosing/attending my university. Here is a list of 5 of those things. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/davecover.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;#1: There is NO PRESSURE to go to University right away:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking back to when I graduated high school, at age 18, I shouldn’t have been trusted to pick out my own clothes in the morning let alone make life-altering decisions with massive financial implications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No I mean it. This was my grade 12 yearbook photo… (click to zoom if on computer)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/yearbook.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;350&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cut-off Ralph Lauren Flannel. CLASSIC!&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But seriously, I had no business making a decision of that magnitude. Taking a year off (or more) could have done wonders for me. I could have been travelling, working to save money, but most importantly I could have used that time to learn, grow, and find out what kind things I enjoy and what things I don’t. Instead, I started finding out three and four years into my degree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That imaginary pressure you feel, telling you that you need to choose a school and degree right out of high school; that’s not the force, it’s the dark side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;#2 You should be WELL-INFORMED when choosing your program:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is what my terribly uninformed decision-making breakdown looked like, when choosing my program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/list.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;550&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As hard as it is to believe, I was slightly misled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know now, that an Arts Degree and a Business/Commerce degree are pretty much of equal value, when competing for most entry-level positions. Obviously there are limitations. You won’t become an accountant with a philosophy undergrad, &lt;em&gt;but&lt;/em&gt; an English major who worked for the school paper for 2 years probably has the edge on a marketing major with no additional experience. Even for a position in marketing! Your experience and your extra curricular activities are what will set you apart. Get involved in clubs and societies. You&#39;ll meet some awesome people and build your resume at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also now know that engineering is not a program for railroad conductors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;#3 You CAN get a job (some pretty good ones too) without going to University:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although having a university degree or college diploma is absolutely necessary for most entry-level positions, for some others it is not.  Please note, I did not say that you &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; get a job, but simply stated that it&#39;s doable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that the number of tech related jobs is exploding. A lesser-known fact though, is that for many of these jobs, employers are not only willing to hire applicants without degrees, but actually sometimes prefer these applicants. Don’t mistake this for meaning that tech companies are hiring candidates with blank resumes. If you’re looking for a job as a programmer, you’d better have plenty of experience in several programming languages as well as a developed portfolio that demonstrates your capabilities. Don&#39;t mistake this for the easy way out. Think of it more as an alternate route, with its own set perks and challenges&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, there are also tons of awesome online courses (some free, some not) for learning programming and web design/development. Successfully completing a few of these shows employers that you are self-motivated and able to see things through. If this interests you, check out some of the programs offered by &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.udacity.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; UDACITY.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;#4 When it comes to partying, you need to find BALANCE:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe you’re a 100% sober Zen master, or maybe you’re an extremely high-functioning alcoholic – impervious to hangovers. If not, you’re just like the rest of us mere mortals, and you need to strike a balance between partying and productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;Now, I’m not saying anyone should abstain from partying altogether. I tried that for the greater part of my first two years, and it would be a huge understatement to say that I, inevitably, “made up for lost time” in year three and part of year four. Believe me, you will hit a wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going out and getting plastered can be a blast, and is part of the whole experience, but if you want to get the most out of your time in University, don’t let drinking define your four years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;u&gt;&lt;h2&gt;#5 EVERYONE should study abroad (if they can):&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many opportunities for undergrads to study abroad. I honestly cannot believe that I didn&#39;t take advantage of this. You often pay the same tuition as you would at your own school, you’ll spend enough time there to actually be immersed in the culture (maybe even learn a language), and if you’re lucky, you’ll end up receiving pass/fail grades, which basically means you&#39;re on vacation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;meta name=&quot;description&quot; content=&quot;choosing a university, how to choose your university, canadian university, choosing university in canada&quot; /&gt;






















		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/04/Things-I-Wish.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/04/Things-I-Wish.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Refresh: to make fresh again; reinvigorate or cheer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Several things over the past few days have been very refreshing for me; and in several different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/dingle.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most refreshing moment of all - in a literal sense - was diving in for my first outdoor swim of the year. Some friends and I packed some snacks and biked down Purcell&#39;s Cove Road to a little swimming hole called Williams Lake, which I hadn&#39;t been to before. It&#39;s just past the turnoff to the Dingle (on the opposite side of Purcell&#39;s Cove Rd). The water wasn&#39;t exactly boiling, but it was definitely bearable, and it just felt nice to swim again after about 9 months out of water. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/dive.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Kinda looks like I belly flopped... Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon returning from our trip I can remember, with vivid detail, staring in awe of the old trees covered with young leaves hanging over Quinpool Rd. Just as these trees had been refreshed, so had I. I was reminded of how beautiful our city is, and of how profoundly some colour, life, and vitamin D can impact my state of mind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/lemonade.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;650&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we continued up Quinpool, we came across these adorable little girls selling lemonade for $0.25 to raise money for the IWK and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://convio.cancer.ca/site/TR/Thirdpartyevent/IFE_NS_General_?pg=entry&amp;fr_id=20012#.VWxwzFxVhHw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailblazer 4 Cancer fundraiser&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Tommy put their mixology skills to the test and ordered the signature cocktail &quot;Pink Lightning&quot;, a mix of not only regular lemonade, but pink as well. The girls informed us that after our first purchase, our second cup was free! An eerily similar business model to that of Vogue Optical&#39;s. Lawsuit pending...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also made a quick pit stop at a good-old-fashioned yard sale, where paperback books were selling again for $0.25. Overcome by the awesome nostalgia associated with yard sales and being able to purchase awesome things for a quarter, I picked up Stephen R. Covey&#39;s
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/36072.The_7_Habits_of_Highly_Effective_People&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;7 Habits of Highly Effective People.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/theboys.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Ho-Jin, Tommy and I before heading down to the lake&lt;br&gt;Photo By: Vicki Jeha&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I can&#39;t forget our awesome Lawn Summer Nights Team, who participated in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://cysticfibrosis.ca/greatstrides/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carstar Great Strides Walk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to support Cystic Fibrosis research and to spread awareness for Lawn Summer Nights. It was great for our team to have a chance to speak with some families and individuals directly impacted by Cystic Fibrosis. It helped us gain some valuable perspective and reminded us again why Lawn Summer Nights exists and the positive impact that events like this have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/team.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; SQUAD. &lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halifax Lawn Summer Nights has been nominated for a Maritime Philanthropy Award and will be throwing its official &quot;Lawnch Party&quot; at the Scanway Patio on June 12th from 6-8pm! All attendees must RSVP to halifax@lawnsummernights.com. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
















		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/01/swim-and-lemonade.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/06/01/swim-and-lemonade.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just What I needed</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s been ten days since my last post. Between a mix of spring courses at SMU, work, and some general anxiety, I&#39;d found myself in a bit of a rut the past few days. Having recognized that I was slipping, I tried waking up at 5am, in an attempt to get ahead and lay out my week, but found myself distracted and unable to give my full attention to any one of my competing priorities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I know it sounds cliché, but I figured some time outside with friends might be all I needed to get myself back on track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/turret.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a quick trip out to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?q=duncan%27s+cove&amp;espv=2&amp;biw=1680&amp;bih=843&amp;source=lnms&amp;tbm=isch&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=g3JjVcO7NOPLsASPyICwBQ&amp;ved=0CAcQ_AUoAg&amp;dpr=2&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Duncan&#39;s Cove Nature Reserve&lt;/a&gt;(photos below), I found myself both mentally and physically refreshed. We followed up the hike with an awesome BBQ, and we were even given free burgers at Sobeys! Yeah, and then I got food poisoning... &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/dead.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Nothing like waking up wearing a hoodie and sweatpants, covered in cold sweat, dehydrated, and confused all at the same time! And yes, that is me in that photo.&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m feeling better now, and with improving weather and spring courses coming to an end soon enough, I am super excited to start checking off some of my summer to-do&#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a very proud moment earlier this week. Ho-Jin had just come home from sorting out his visa situation and ever-so-eloquently described the experience as &quot;a shit show&quot;. You don&#39;t learn that one at ESL school!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check out some photos from the hike down below, but before that, I&#39;ll throw down a few links to some cool stuff I&#39;ve stumbled upon recently. Check &#39;em out!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/MoviePosterPorn/top/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Reddit Movie Poster Porn:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; No this is not actually porn... It&#39;s a list of all the best fan-made movie posters. In my opinion, most of them are way better than the originals!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickchart.com/Charts.aspx?genre=Anime&amp;perpage=100&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt; - 100 Best Anime Movies of All Time:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; This is awesome. If you haven&#39;t tried watching anime movies before, I highly recommend trying a few of these out. I just watched &lt;em&gt;My Neighbor Totoro&lt;/em&gt; for the first time, and felt like I was a kid again. If you&#39;re looking for something more serious, try &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oP2Pt6m3yKU&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;em&gt;Ghost in the Shell.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Apparently it served as inspiration in the creation of &lt;em&gt;The Matrix.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icheckmovies.com/lists/reddit+top+250/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Reddit&#39;s Top 250 Movies - Courtesy of iCheck Movies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; I&#39;ve been using this list for a while now and it is MONEY. I find, when browsing IMDB or Rotten Tomatoes, I tend to agree with ratings and lists maybe 65% of the time. Obviously this is very subjective, but I&#39;ve found this movie list to be the best I&#39;ve come across for sure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://agenda.weforum.org/2015/05/what-13-successful-leaders-read-every-morning/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Reading/Morning Routines of 13 Successful Leaders:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; I found this list interesting and motivating. Makes me want to do some more magazine reading. There are some interesting links within this article as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt; Hike Photos! &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/clear2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/selfie.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/wave.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/goat.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;This stump looked just like a goat to me^^^&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/clear.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/look.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/climb.JPG&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;






		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/05/25/hike-to-duncans.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/05/25/hike-to-duncans.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Value of Writing Things Down &lt;br&gt;(a non-scientific angle)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Every time you have a cool idea, a profound thought, or see something you want to remember, write it down! It may seem daunting at first, but once you make it a priority to right down anything and everything that may be of use to you, you will soon reap the benefits, of which there are plenty.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/writing.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may have noticed that I have re-designed my blog a little bit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&#39;re not on a phone, try clicking the above image^^^&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Boom.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h6&gt;(shoutout to Dawson Reid for the coding help)&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, back to business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since childhood, I&#39;ve been quite forgetful. Generally, with trivial things mind you. I&#39;d get to the hockey rink, only to find out I forgot my skates, I&#39;d show up to class without my field trip permission slip, or even take the bus home without my backpack. In the image below, you will see a 100% genuine screenshot of a few of my recent iPhone alarms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/ifen.png&quot; height=&quot;230&quot; width=&quot;230&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt; That&#39;s right... &quot;7:49&quot;, &quot;8:36&quot; &amp; &quot;8:37&quot;. You might have noticed, &quot;call g rents&quot;, in there as well. Just a simple reminder to call my grandparents because it wass important to me, and I didn&#39;t want to forget to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;If it&#39;s so important to you, why do you need an alarm to remember it?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love my grandparents, but that doesn&#39;t mean I can&#39;t get distracted by one of the 10,000 other things I think about on a day-to-day basis. I&#39;m 22 years old. I&#39;m in classes, I work, I&#39;ve made a commitment to pretend I know anything about anything on this blog, and on occasion I waste anywhere from 5 to 35 minutes imagining what I would do if I went back in time, to when I was 7 years old, knowing everything I know now. Just because something is important to me, doesn&#39;t mean it won&#39;t slip my mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt; There’s a ridiculous amount of hard science, proving that writing any given thing down increases your chances of remembering it, even if you never look at it again. Instead of scraping the internet for some second-hand science, I&#39;ll try to describe the benefits of writing things down, from my own experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Here is a list of ways you can benefit, by being proactive in writing things down:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#1 - You&#39;re able to &quot;prioritize your priorities&quot;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; If you make a point of writing down all of the things you need/want to get done, you can actually sort them in order of importance. By tackling my goals individually, and in order of urgency/importance, I find I&#39;m able to work a lot more efficiently. You can also reduce the weight of all your to-do&#39;s, by eliminating the ones you simply don&#39;t have time for. Now that you&#39;ve eliminated them, these thoughts no longer linger, clouding your mind and wasting your limited brain power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;#2 - You can constantly refine your processes. And it&#39;s fun!!!.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; Have you ever found and read some of your old schoolwork? It&#39;s interesting to see how you&#39;ve grown over the years. Perhaps even more interesting, is seeing how much your thoughts and mindset can change in a much smaller timeframe. Everytime you look back on your notes, you&#39;re in at least a slightly different mindset than when you initially wrote them down. Each time you look back, you offer a different perspective on your own ideas. That&#39;s how the refining process works! And it&#39;s exciting to feel yourself learning and growing!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;#3 - You can enhance the experience you get from reading a book.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; Even if you&#39;re just reading for leisure, it can&#39;t hurt to learn something! Try using a blank, stiff piece of paper as a bookmark, and writing down each word you cannot provide a clear definition for. You can either look the words up as you go, or take some time every few days to look them all up at once. Although I prefer the feel of a real book, I often use my tablet for harder reads, as I can easily retrieve a word&#39;s definition and highlight sections of the book that I might like to review.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/img_1059.png&quot; height=&quot;230&quot; width=&quot;230&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt; &lt;h6&gt;please excuse my terrible hand-writing&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#4 - It can really help you get to know yourself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; As cliché as it sounds, I&#39;ve discovered that this is an excellent way to better understand myself, my thoughts and my priorities. Taking the time to sit down alone and reflect on your own thoughts and ideas in a systematic fashion can seem like a strange concept at first, but it is in itself, a process that you continue to refine in order to understand both yourself and your environment on a more intimate level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

	&lt;br&gt;

Set goals, write them down, and list them in order of importance. 5 Months ago I had a list of goals, and at the top of that list was &quot;learn to code to make a blog&quot;. And here we are.

&lt;/p&gt;
















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/05/12/6--writing-things-down.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/05/12/6--writing-things-down.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Things in Halifax That You Probably Haven&#39;t Tried</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Halifax is not a huge city by any means. Many people here feel as though they&#39;ve seen and done it all. If you count yourself among those who feel that way, I bet you&#39;re wrong!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/lawnsum.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it&#39;s food, drink, music, places to explore, or maybe an event you&#39;ve never been too, I can guarantee that there is still something new and awesome for you to try here in Halifax.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;In no particular order, here is a list of some of my favourite things you may not have already tried:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#1 Spicy Chili Chicken – The Great Wall Chinese: &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If KFC’s Popcorn Chicken and Sriracha Chili Sauce made a baby, you’d get The Great Wall’s Spicy Chili Chicken on their traditional menu. One of the most flavourful foods I’ve ever eaten. Try it with a bowl of rice and chopsticks, but be careful not to chomp on one of the full chili peppers mixed in with the chicken.  Unless you’re just raw like that, I guess.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
For a quicker and cheaper (but still delicious) version, try the Seoul Chicken at Korean Garden Express in Scotia Square!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#2 Lawn Summer Nights – St. Mary’s Lawn Bowls Club:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last summer, St. Mary’s Lawn Bowls Club hosted Halifax’s very first Lawn Summer Nights Lawn Bowling Tournament in an effort to raise money and awareness in order to help those living with Cystic Fibrosis in Canada. Last year’s events were a huge success, with the Halifax chapter contributing $25,000 to a nationwide $1,000,000 raised by Lawn Summer Nights since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/lawnsum2.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights was originally inspired by a courageous woman named Eva Markvoort, who spent her life with Cystic Fibrosis and made it her personal mission to find a cure for the disease. For more info on Eva’s story, and the history of Lawn Summer Nights, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://lawnsummernights.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;Lawnsummernights.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights was one of the most, if not the most, exciting part of my 2014 summer. Teams of four dressed up in vintage attire, competed over the span of four consecutive Thursday nights, and enjoyed food, drinks, live music, and some powerful words from leaders in our community living with Cystic Fibrosis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lawn Summer Nights is an event powered by passionate individuals from Halifax’s young professional community, looking to raise money for a great cause, which has seen several major advances over the past decade. Registration opens at noon on Monday, May 11th and the cost is $400 per team. If you are interested in attending, have your team ready to register on Monday! Toronto, Victoria and Vancouver’s events sold out in the first 3 minutes! This years events will take place on Thursday, July 2nd, 9th, 16th, and 23, with and 30th as a rain date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn.png&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/york/lawn.png&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;#3 Beef Jerky - Lion &amp; Bright Café: &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thick slices, not too dry and super tasty. I’ve probably had Lion and Bright’s beef jerky about 10 times now.  I’m always convincing strangers to try it, and I might be the only person to try to order it for breakfast. Don’t Spend $5 on gas station jerky when you can get the real deal at Lion and Bright on Agricola for the same price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;h4&gt;#4 My Father’s Bowtie Collection – Biscuit General Store:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This past year, in lieu of the standard black or blue tie, at StFX’s famous X-Ring Ceremony, about 95% of the guys were rocking bowties. The man behind this was recent StFX graduate and Entrepreneur, Demetrius Ferguson. Demetrius started selling his bowties in November of 2014, one week before X-Ring. My Father’s Bowtie Collection provides a unique selection of patterns and fabrics with a vintage twist. Handcrafted in Prince Edward Island, this is a true artisan product and, at only $35, makes for a fantastic gift!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/ties.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Father’s Bowtie Collection is now available in Halifax at Biscuit General Store on Argyle Street. Check out some more ties on MFC&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/mfc_bowties/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;instagram page!&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/aj.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;h4&gt;#5 Graphic Novels at The Halifax Central Library:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just finished Frank Miller’s &lt;em&gt;Batman: The Dark Knight Returns&lt;/em&gt;, duuuude… 
I can’t believe it has taken me this long to get into graphic novels. The Halifax Central Library has shelves full of these things. I also hear that the Keshen Goodman Library in Clayton Park has an even better collection. If you’re thinking, “Pfft, I don’t have time to read comics”, this 224 pager only took me 4-5 hours (and I’m not a fast reader). If you watch “The Big Bang Theory”, I would suggest just dropping that bad habit in order to make more time. That show is terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I scooped these ones, in the image below, from The Halifax Central Library today. You can also see that I&#39;ve downloaded some comics to read on my tablet. Super easy to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center&quot; src=&quot;/img/comics.png&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, keep in mind that not all comics and graphic novels are about superheroes.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out a list of some other awesome graphic novels &lt;a href=&quot;https://forbiddenplanet.com/log/recommendations/50-best-best-graphic-novels/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here!&lt;/a&gt; (have a look at #1)&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Get out and give these a try!&lt;/h4&gt;











	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/05/08/6-things-halifax.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/05/08/6-things-halifax.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
