<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dave Culligan</title>
    <description>Blog website, following the life and adventures of David Culligan. 
</description>
    <link>http://daveculligan.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://daveculligan.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 10:18:33 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 10:18:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why You Can&#39;t Fake Confidence</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re all well aware of the importance and benefits associated with being confident. When we’re preparing for an interview, giving an important presentation,  or just mustering up the courage to ask someone out, we’re often told “just be confident!” &lt;strong&gt;Read this post and see why this is actually terrible advice.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/kanfidence.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been depressed or really upset and had someone say to you, “Hey, don’t be sad!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did it work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn’t think so…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not that the person saying it doesn’t want to help, but I like to call this “lazy advice”. Lazy advice, like “don’t be sad!” or “just be confident!” is a huge problem. When we lack self-esteem, and someone tells us to “just be confident”, this only amplifies the problem. First of all, it can make us feel like there’s something wrong with us. We ask ourselves “Why can’t I &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;JUST&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; be confident?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, the simplicity of this advice implies that being confident is easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AND IT’S NOT!!!&lt;/strong&gt; It’s really really hard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/cswitch.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there is no magic switch you can turn on and suddenly be confident. You have to work at it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you do that? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all have our own &lt;strong&gt;“comfort zone”&lt;/strong&gt;, our spectrum of activities and tasks we can carry out, without feeling anxiety, nervousness, or any form of discomfort.  The only way we can ever become more confident and expand our comfort zone is to force ourselves to do things that are &lt;strong&gt;NOT COMFORTABLE.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/tcruise.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h4&gt; Get out of your comfort zone, and enter the DANGER ZONE!&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The more time we spend acting outside of our comfort zones, the more familiar we become with these certain activities or challenges until, eventually, we annex them, marking these previously terrifying tasks as new territory inside our comfort zone. I can still remember how much I hated my parents for making me go into town with resumes, to basically beg for my first job. It was terrible. But, now that I&#39;ve done that so many times, walking into a business and asking to speak to the decision maker feels routine, like tying my shoes. Thanks Ma &amp; Pa!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to thank my friend Adam Otmar, who recently challenged me to think about this: You can’t “fake” confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason you can’t “fake” confidence, is because faking confidence &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;IS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/toaster.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being confident doesn’t necessarily mean never being afraid of anything, or never feeling anxiety. If you’re able to take a deep breathe and face a situation that makes you uncomfortable, no matter how anxious you feel, you are acting with confidence just by forcing yourself to face something you know won’t be easy. And when you do this, instead of feeling guilty for being nervous, you should feel proud for being so brave!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In my third year of university I gave a presentation, worth almost 40% of my grade, and after class, a girl approached me and said “Wow, you speak with so much confidence!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was shocked. During that presentation, I was so nervous that my mouth dried up, my knees shook violently behind the podium, and I &lt;em&gt;literally&lt;/em&gt; pissed in my pants a little bit (only time this has ever happened).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only reason I was able to project confidence was that I practiced for several hours before the presentation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This brings me to another point. If you’re not skilled at something, and you haven’t worked on it, maybe you shouldn’t be confident? Perhaps you haven’t earned the right to feel fully confident in that task yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/batmanconfidence.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Batman&#39;s Super Power is confidence&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, Batman’s super power is confidence, but he isn’t just blindly confident or arrogant. Batman busted his ass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0372784/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Batman Begins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (The first Christopher Nolan one), when Christian Bale gets his ass whooped by Ninja-Monks up in the mountains? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, Batman earned his stripes. And if you haven&#39;t seen &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0372784/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Batman Begins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;... You need to watch &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0372784/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Batman Begins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;And last, but certainly not least, as much as Batman exemplifies confidence, we need to be careful when looking at these &quot;super&quot; role models. And not just fictional super heroes, but other figures like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.ca/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=elon%20musk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Elon Musk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.ca/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=lebron+james&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lebron James&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or, for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/caseyneistat&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Casey Neistat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a famous and innovative filmmaker, rule-breaker, and jack-of-all-trades. Role models are a great source of inspiration, and I&#39;m all for shooting for the stars, but constantly comparing ourselves and our achievements to people like this will only make us feel inadequate 99 times out of 100.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;






&lt;p&gt;This is something I battle with all the time. When I first started making video blogs with my old iPhone 5, I was getting upset that they weren&#39;t as awesome as Casey Neistat&#39;s, which makes no sense at all! He&#39;s been making movies for 20 years, he has access to professional equipment, and he&#39;s one of the best at what he does in the whole world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Am I still inspired by Casey&#39;s videos? Yes. Do I still compare mine to his? N......Not as much. I&#39;m working on it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Dave&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 08:55:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/12/02/Cant-fake-confidence.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/12/02/Cant-fake-confidence.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Motivation Monday #2: Move </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Don’t you wish you could spend more time outside? Wouldn’t it be nice if you could stop drinking so much? Don’t you wish you could write a book? Wouldn’t it be so cool if you could stop listening to others, and just do what &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; want to do? Well, you can, you just have to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/justdoit.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two days ago, I’d never owned or even used a real camera before. I just got my first camera, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.nikon.ca/nikon-products/product/dslr-cameras/d5200.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Nikon D5200&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and instead of worrying about all the different features and settings I had no idea how to use, this morning I woke up at 5am, pumped out 40 pushups to let my body know that we weren&#39;t going back to sleep, and headed into downtown Halifax to get some shots. I couldn&#39;t be more pleased with the result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali1.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali2.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali13.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt; See the rest at the bottom of this post &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m sure a professional photographer would have some critiques, but I’m pretty damn happy with these, and I feel like a million dollars right now, ready to crush my day. And, if I’d stayed in bed all morning, which my body desperately wanted me to do, or if I’d waited until I’d read the whole user&#39;s manual, these shots never would have been taken.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Does &quot;you miss 100% of the shots you don&#39;t take&quot; apply to photography? Why not.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so important to keep moving all the time. Research is important, but it doesn’t accomplish much unless you get out and &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt;. Aristotle said, in The Nichomachian Ethics, “For the things we have to learn before we can do them, we learn by doing them.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On that note, here’s an extremely inspiring three-minute video from Arc’teryx, called Move, about a 46-year-old dad, who refuses to stop pushing his limits and living to the fullest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xCpowcXopKE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I loved that video, and want to thank my friend Craig for sharing it with me. I’ve really been struggling with the idea of winter ruining my ability to hike and explore, but this video reminded me that it doesn’t have to at all. I’m a healthy, capable young man, who owns boots, gloves, and a winter jacket. Problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real problem was, I was letting some bullshit, preconceived notion that winter is scary and cold is bad scare me away from enjoying the outdoors. I allowed myself to be influenced by what most others think and do, which is an awesome way to suck. That’s not to say that all other people suck, but to limit yourself to what other people think you should do is to limit yourself to absolute mediocrity – and I assume you don’t want that if you’re reading this post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This next video, running about 6 minutes, is an example of an incredible individual, Casey Neistat, who, in utter frustration at being told what he could and couldn’t do, forged his own path, and is living out his dreams everyday.
If you couldn’t watch the video, Casey recalls being told as a kid “if you think you’re going to grow up and be able to skateboard in halls of your office, you’ve got another thing coming”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RPH7eIVahIM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He then tells us that he’s built a half-pipe inside his New York office, just so he can skateboard at work whenever he wants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does this seem familiar to you? Has society, your parents, or your friends tried to place limitations on what your career has to look like, what your interests have to be, or what feelings you should keep to yourself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It feels extremely familiar to me, and my blood boils just at the thought of it. To emphasize just how much I hate that kind of limiting attitude toward a person trying to live, grow, and be themselves, I say &lt;strong&gt;FUCK THAT.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don&#39;t like the language, pardon my passion. I will not apologize for exercising the freedom I am &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; fortunate to have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/art.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The main reason we listen to these naysayers, is that we’re afraid they’re right. We have this negativity and these limitations poured on us so often that we start to believe them. This is why it is &lt;em&gt;so important&lt;/em&gt; that we understand our own value, and remind ourselves of our own potential every single day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/note.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Image above is my personal journal, which used to read “Don’t Underestimate The Force”. In an exhilarating moment of self-love, self-realization, and appreciation of my own value, I wanted to solidify that feeling as a staple in my life, and created a daily reminder so that I never lose sight of this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all have our ups and downs, but if you give up on yourself, so will everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Dave&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali3.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali4.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali5.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali6.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali7.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali9.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali10.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali11.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali12.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali14.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali15.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali16.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali17.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali18.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali19.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali20.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/hali21.JPG&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



















































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 08:55:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/30/move.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/30/move.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Selfie-brating my 23rd Birthday</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Firstly, thank you so much to everyone who posted one of these ridiculous selfies on my Facebook for my birthday. As many of you know, &lt;a href=&quot; http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/24/Death-to-Selfies.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;in my last post&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, I took a jab at selfies, and offered some alternatives for those seeking connection. Then, two days later, I facetiously asked all of my Facebook friends to post a selfie on my wall for my birthday. I wanted to to show something here; and that&#39;s the massive potential - both positive and negative - of social media, something of great interest to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/selfiecollage.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;650&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h5&gt; This image is a collage of the responses I received after asking my facebook friends to post selfies on my wall for my birthday&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said in my last post, selfies themselves are not inherently bad, and it&#39;s the intention behind them that is important. And this holds true for all aspects of social media, and technology in general for that matter. If you haven&#39;t read &lt;a href=&quot;http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/24/Death-to-Selfies.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;my last post&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, I would encourage you to do so before finishing this one. If you don&#39;t have time, I touched on the value of introspective thinking in comparison to chasing instant gratification, in the form of likes, especially if based soley on one&#39;s appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though I recognize and take a firm stance against the potentially dangerous implications of social media, in going forward, my blog will focus, largely, on the massive positive influence that is achievable through the use social media and technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it weren&#39;t for social media, my birthday would have been entirely different. I still would have spent time with great friends, but in addition to that, I was able to connect with friends from all over the country, and all over the world. And, through use of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/analytics/?gclid=Cj0KEQiAvuWyBRDO_Yzhpv_4nvEBEiQANBdXMjZ8kGYWi6hCLobCPOszdM4duNxkixpUNJgj6fklyx0aAnN18P8HAQ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, I&#39;ll be able to see all of the different countries of the world from which different people read this post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/selfies3.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;650&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I also noticed an interesting phenomenon in action, just after launching my little selfie experiment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the start, most of the birthday wishes came in the traditional text form, and just a few went out on a limb and posted some funny selfies. But, after a few hours went by, more and more of my friends jumped in on the action. After they&#39;d seen some of the others put themselves out there, in a silly, perhaps even self-deprecating manner, they had no problem doing so themselves. The result, in my opinion, was awesome (as can be seen from the photos above). Seen below, is a quick Ted Talk that focuses on exactly this phenomenon. Again, I strongly encourage that you watch it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/V74AxCqOTvg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I won&#39;t be so arrogant as to call my experiment a movement, but I definitely think it demonstrates the power of social media, and its potential to promote positivity and collectivism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also want to mention that I&#39;m working on a few different projects right now that I am &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; excited about. Without giving too much away, they involve a lot of social media, my brand new camera, and a strong emphasis on growth. Vague enough for you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to thank everyone who took the time to subject themselves to my ridiculousness, and especially those brave few who first took the leap. And ESPECIALLY ESPECIALLY &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/erincarroll94/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Erin Carroll.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Not a typo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are all awesome, and I am so excited to share more of this with you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;-Dave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



















































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 08:55:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/28/it's-a-Selfie-bration.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/28/it's-a-Selfie-bration.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introspection vs Instant Gratification</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, I might as well begin by admitting that &lt;em&gt;yes&lt;/em&gt;, I &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; taken a selfie before. I think we all have, and it&#39;s not like they&#39;re inherently bad. If you scale a mountain by yourself and no one&#39;s there to capture the moment, selfie away! But, if you&#39;re just sitting home feeling lonely or seeking recognition, there are much healthier ways to deal with that then posting a selfie on Instragram. This post is about those things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/selfies.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to preface by saying that this post is not an attack on anyone. We all seek recognition and find it in different places. I also understand that our society sometimes places different pressures on girls/women than it does on men. &lt;strong&gt;BUT...&lt;/strong&gt; Even if you are fortunate enough to be very attractive, is that really the only thing you want to be recognized for? And if it is, for how long can that happiness really last until you feel the need to fill that void again?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re seeking connection on the internet, which I obviously do, try to share something demonstrative of your value. Create something. Draw a picture, write a story, share an opinion or an idea. I promise, the satisfaction of having created something, something all of your own, will be far greater than any amount of likes can provide. And as an added bonus, just by having tried it, you&#39;ve actually gotten better at something - and that lasts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/ericthomas.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now&lt;/strong&gt;, if we&#39;re really brave, we can learn to &lt;em&gt;embrace&lt;/em&gt; being alone. This doesn&#39;t mean becoming a hermit or shutting ourselves out completeley, but perhaps just staying home on a Friday night, reflecting and collecting our thoughts. As difficult as it can be to pass up a night out, when we take the time to clear our minds, we realize pretty quickly that the world isn&#39;t going to pass us by in a single night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have time, I encourage you to watch the video below. It&#39;s about a man who spent 44 years in prison, and his reaction to how the world has changed. I was inspired by the way he has accepted his less-than-ideal circumstances, and the positive attitude with which he faces them. He speaks with a sense of calm that seems too profound to be ingenuine, and he uses meditation to help achieve this.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OrH6UMYAVsk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Over the past few months I&#39;ve dabbled with meditation and I can&#39;t say enough good things about what it&#39;s done for me. Being alone with your own thoughts can help you learn a lot about yourself, but it&#39;s actually not even necessary that you think. &lt;a href=&quot; https://www.google.ca/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=alan%20watts&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Alan Watts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; once said &quot;A person who thinks all the time has nothing to think about except thoughts&quot;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perhaps that quote doesn&#39;t quite make sense to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Perhaps that&#39;s the point?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Perhaps in order to understand what Mr. Watts was getting at here, you&#39;ll need to explore the concept a little bit further.   
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I speak from experience when I testify to the value of meditation and spending time alone. I used to, and still sometimes do, suffer from severe F.O.M.O. (fear of missing out), and overcoming that has been &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; difficult. When I say extremely, I mean it took me years of actively trying figure myself out. I tried everything from solo hikes to listening to motivational speaking, reading blog posts like this, self-help books, and journal writing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s difficult to say which one of these has been the most helpful in my crusade for self-discovery, and I wouldn&#39;t dare prescribe one or the other to anyone, but you certainly can&#39;t go wrong with a healthy combination of reading, meditation (in its many forms), and spending time out in nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in meditation, self-exploration, or even just learning, I highly recccomend a book called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/390562.What_the_Buddha_Taught_With_Texts_from_Suttas_Dhammapada&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What The Buddha Taught&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/author/show/122674.Walpola_Rahula&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walpola Rahula&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; . The book is a snapshot of the origins and purpose of Buddhism, and it&#39;s about as comprehensvive as a 192 page book can be, with its very anecdotal style. For those terrified by the idea of religion, Buddhism is thought by many to be more of a philosophy than a religion - a mechanism to deal with the the inevitable hardships dished out by life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/buddha.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also posted a great 15-minute guided mediation with some cool, esoteric music at &lt;a href=&quot;http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/20/Back-in-Business.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;the bottom of this post&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for those who are interested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I had to guess, I would say this post may have some people feeling a little defensive. That&#39;s okay, but if you&#39;re one of these people, next time you seek connection, I challenge you to try connecting with yourself and your own feelings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; You just might be surprised at how it makes you feel. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Dave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



















































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 08:55:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/24/Death-to-Selfies.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/24/Death-to-Selfies.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Motivation Monday</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in the summer, I made a post, titled “Motivation for Your Monday”, and it seemed to be quite well-received – which comes as no surprise. Finding the motivation to wake up early and to use our time productively can be extremely difficult. Especially for those of us who live in a place with cold, dark, and long winters, which can really take a toll on our psyche. Since this struggle is something we all face, and it can be so difficult to overcome, each Monday, I’ll be writing a Motivation Monday post to provide a little kick start to your week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/motivationmonday.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re all motivated by different types of stimuli, and require different forms of motivation to overcome different obstacles. The Internet is full of motivational videos, quotes, and other content, but that’s not always enough. This week, I’m going to talk about two tricks I use to keep myself moving, even when it feels near impossible to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;1) The Ulysses Contract:&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is something I’ve done for a long time, but only learned the name for it a few months ago. A Ulysses contract is a decision that you make, in order to bind your future self. The name comes from a story about Ulysses, a hero from Greek literature, in which he wanted to listen to the songs of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Siren_(mythology)&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Sirens&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The Sirens were beautiful, mermaid-like creatures, who sang songs that drove men mad, forcing them to crash their ships into the rocks, from which the Sirens sang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/ulysses.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Ulysses tied to the mast, driven mad by the songs of the Sirens &lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the story goes, Ulysses asked his men to tie him, tightly, to the ship’s mast, and had them stuff their own ears with wax. In doing this, Ulysses was able to hear the song of the legendary Sirens, and his future self was unable to escape the ropes, preventing him from crashing the ship into the rocks, which he surely would have.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really like that story, and I really like using Ulysses Contracts. &lt;strong&gt;A few examples of these would be:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Plugging your phone/alarm in on the other side of the room, so you have to get out of bed in the morning to turn it off. Or maybe using one of those apps that requires you to answer a math problem before you can stop your alarm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Asking a friend to meet you at the gym/library/office early in the morning. You may still have to move your phone across the room, but the added accountability might be just what you need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Announcing your goals publicly, or maybe just to friends. Maybe this isn’t right for everyone, but I find the fear of letting people down to be a great source of motivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;2) Setting Finite/ S.M.A.R.T. Goals:&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/smrt.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of you have probably heard of the acronym S.M.A.R.T., in reference to goals that are: Specific, Measurable, Attainable, Relevant, and Time-Based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than setting a vague goal (which isn’t necessarily bad) such as “I want to become more employable”, you can set a S.M.A.R.T. goal, perhaps more like “I’m going to sign up for, and complete three, free online courses from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coursera.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Coursera&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; next month”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I find this makes for much more productive use of your time. When I first decided to learn to code, I kept flip flopping from site to site, video to video, trying to find the right/best way to learn. This led to a whole lot of wasted time, and not a lot of actual learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t until I decided to build a project website (which eventually became this one), that I started actually learning. Instead of wasting valuable time bouncing around different pages, I was coming across specific problems like “how do I embed a YouTube video on my page?” and would google them individually, and work on them until I was ready to move to the next step.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that these tips can help you get a little bit more out of your week, or even that they may have just reminded you to utilize them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here&#39;s something to try this week, instead of sleeping in or, lord help us all, watching any show from TLC:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.duolingo.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Duolingo - Language Learning App&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/duolingo2.png&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This app is awesome. I&#39;m looking to improve my French, and the app actually makes it quite fun with little games - a point system - and use of voice technology. You can set a goal of 10,15, or 20 minutes per day, and the app will send you notifications to remind you to practice. I&#39;ve also played around with German a little bit, I just love the sound of the language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have an awesome week.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;-Dave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



















































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 08:55:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/22/Motivation-Monday-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/22/Motivation-Monday-1.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back in Business</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;WOW!!! I’ve literally been running around the house, by myself, saying “wow” over and over because I am so stoked about the idea of starting up my blog again! I’ve got so many ideas and thoughts I want to share, and I’m sick of scribbling them all down in my notepads, where they, far too often, go to die. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/blogisback.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No longer shall my beautiful Moleskine notepad serve as a graveyard for my creative thoughts, but, once again, as a holster and springboard for my ideas and passions!&lt;/P&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s fantastically frustrating, the challenge of taking a certain level of positive energy, and translating it into writing. I am so up for this challenge; this test of the creative will, if you will. And &lt;em&gt;I WILL&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know that you’re ready to start blogging again, when the idea excites you &lt;em&gt;so much&lt;/em&gt; that you start yelling out things like “MAKIN’ STUFF!” or even just a subtle, self-assured “aww yeah”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d been playing with the idea for a while now, but I’ve got to give thanks to my pal Dean Casey, for providing the little nudge I needed. Dean has recently taken the leap, and started his &lt;a href=&quot;https://wheresdin.wordpress.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;own blog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, while travelling through Australia and Southeast Asia. He’s a hilarious dude, with brains to boot, and he even has the AUDACITY to think differently, and to tell it how it is. &lt;a href=&quot;https://wheresdin.wordpress.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;CHECK HIM OUT HERE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and PILE ON THE LIKES M8!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m finished my undergrad in less than a month, which is still too damn long if you ask me. That being said, I am beyond excited to be done with this chapter, and to face the new challenges and opportunities that lie ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;A few things I&#39;ve been working on and would like to finish and share on here are:&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- My stand-up comedy script&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Some slam poetry/spoken word&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Some ficton writing, maybe a short story?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now, I&#39;m really looking forward to doing this again. PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE message me or email me with any ideas you&#39;d like to see me write about, or with any challenges you think I should take on!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Dave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I implore you to listen to this!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;350&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jPpUNAFHgxM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;


















































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 08:55:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/20/Back-in-Business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/11/20/Back-in-Business.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Project Wrap-Up</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re reading this, you probably already know that not long ago, I started a blog as a summer project. In this final post, I want to highlight some of my accomplishments this summer, and to discuss some of the many challenges, surprises and rewards that came as a result of all of this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/books.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few months before this summer started, I was having a really rough time. My university football career had turned out to be a grueling and extremely disappointing experience as a whole, I wasn’t enjoying my studies, the anxiety of not knowing what I wanted was overwhelming, I was up to my eyeballs in student debt, and I had resorted to all sorts of stupid coping mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, after months of tearing my hair out and waiting for something to change, I decided to just set a shit-ton of goals for myself, and promised myself that nothing and no one was going to stop me from doing whatever I wanted to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As expected, plans changed, and so did parts of my summer project. That being said, I have no regrets, and I &lt;em&gt;NEVER&lt;/em&gt; could have expected for things to have turned out as well as they did. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Here is a quick list of some of the things I did in these 4 months:&lt;/h3&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;1) I learned to code and built a website and blog (month leading up to summer).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) Including this one, I wrote 17 Blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) I Read 13 Books and learned &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4) I filmed &amp; created 10 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCJ2TlP_ul9bDFBFEHP1uG8g/videos&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;YouTube videos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, adding up to about 45 minutes of material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5) I trained distance running for the first time ever and finished a 21km run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6) I finished two summer university courses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7) I helped organize an incredible event in Lawn Summer Nights, which raised almost $40,000 for cystic fibrosis research. At the event I met an awesome dude named Jeremie Saunders, who just launched his &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1674002261/sickboy-podcast&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Kickstarter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for his podcast called “SICKBOY PODCAST”, please check it out and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1674002261/sickboy-podcast&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;MAKE A DONATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; if you can. It’s going to be special.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) I recorded a CBC Radio interview with my friend Ho-Jin and spoke about our friendship and summer plans, the stigma surrounding Asian students in Halifax, and my blog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9) I got a great job, pretty much as a direct result of my blog, and am putting my newly learned skills to use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10) I went on a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4APURUB-5WA&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;camping trip all alone&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; (amazing).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11) I hosted four Couchsurfers, two from Germany and two from Belgium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12) I got beers with two of my favourite teachers from grade school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, though, more frequently than any other time in my life, I experienced some moments of extreme contentment and gratitude. Moments, in which I wanted for nothing, and was just so incredibly grateful to be where I was, to be with the people I was with, and to feel the way I felt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This summer I’ve had the time to read, write, teach, explore, and to think critically and introspectively. I’ve also spent a lot of time alone this summer, which is something I really never did in the past. Throughout this process, I’ve learned that being alone can be very healthy and sometimes the best answer to a lot of problems is “read more”. I’ve also learned that life is pretty much invariably difficult, and that that same difficulty is what makes those brief moments of serenity so fantastic and so worth striving for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you’re like me or 99% of other young people (or just people for that matter) and you know that you have energy, passion, and value, but you’re finding yourself confused, unfulfilled or just wanting new experiences; my advice to you is this: Set a ridiculous amount of fun, challenging, and rewarding goals, then just attack them. Set a schedule, get up early, stop doing things that you don’t want to and that are hurting you, isolate yourself if you really must, but just go make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will warn you now, DO NOT attempt this half-heartedly. I speak from experience when I say that you will only find more distress and disappointment should you seek change and set goals, only to back out at the first sign of resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a project for me and I never knew how far I would go, but for now I’ve decided that with my hectic schedule, I will not continue blogging at this time. For now, I’m enjoying spending my little time that I do have to myself, reading, writing in my personal journal, or just doing whatever else makes me happy at that time. That being said, I might someday feel inspired to revamp this blog and get back on the horse. Who knows? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could ramble on for hours about the value of putting yourself out there, or of taking the time to think, learn, grow, and get to know your self better. In lieu of doing so, I just want to thank everyone who helped me this summer, who supported me, who read my blogs, who pretended to read them and just liked my posts, who took the time to mention that they learned something from me, and of course the beautiful people who shared some of those special moments with me this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the best decision I’ve ever made.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BEST SUMMER OF MY LIFE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Dave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;













































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/08/28/my-summer-project.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/08/28/my-summer-project.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make your wardrobe 10X better for less than $100 (for men)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For far too long, I was under the impression that if you want to look good, you have to spend a lot of money. I paid full price for flashy, coulourful clothes that really didn&#39;t look any better than the clothes I already had. Since then, I&#39;ve actually taken the time to do some reading and have improved my wardrobe a ton as a result. In this post, I&#39;ll share some of the most useful and inexpensive tricks I&#39;ve learned along the way. Hopefully they can help you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/secondrun.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Fit trumps all!!! &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It cannot possibly be stressed enough that fit is the most important thing to consider when purchasing clothes. A well-fitted $5 white tee from value village looks better than a $3000 Hugo Boss suit that looks like a hand-me-down from The Rock. If it doesn&#39;t fit perfectly, and you don&#39;t think it can be tailored to fit perfectly, just don&#39;t buy it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pretty much any suit you buy will need tailoring to fit perfectly, but it is so worth it. For suits, leave tailoring to the professionals. For something simple like a t-shirt or jeans, consider learning to tailor your own stuff at home! A few days ago, after a quick tutorial from a friend and the help a a short YouTube video, I was able to taper the legs of an old pair of jeans that I hadn&#39;t worn for over a year. Now, they&#39;re my favourite jeans. In case you were wondering, they&#39;re the jeans I&#39;m wearing in the cover photo for this post! Below is a closer shot of the cuff of the jeans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/cuff2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;These jeans used to drop straight down, baggy around the ankle. After tapering them down from the knee, the cuff hugs my ankle perfectly&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the YouTube video I used to learn how to taper my pants (it&#39;s extremely simple).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/B3zMSGmieaU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tailoring can be really expensive. Having simple tapering done to one pair of jeans could cost around $20. If you have access to a sewing machine, it&#39;s worth your while to learn! In the meantime, learn to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CnrndUAUe9s&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; pinroll your pants.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; It&#39;s not as clean as having your pants tailored, but looks way better than having your pants sag over your shoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Develop Your Own Shopping Rules &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After learning the hard way, I&#39;ve developed a set of rules for myself that I use when shopping for clothes. Here is the process I use to detemine whether I will buy a piece of clothing or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt; 1. It has to fit perfectly, or be worth tailoring &lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I find a pair of jeans that fit great everywhere but the ankle, they can be fixed up no problem. But do they meet the rest of the criteria?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt; 2. It has to be crazy cheap. Like 50%-90% off.&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I recently bought &lt;a href=&quot;http://bananarepublic.gapcanada.ca/browse/product.do?pid=186133013&amp;vid=1&amp;locale=en_CA&amp;kwid=1&amp;sem=false&amp;sdkw=tailored-fit-light-gray-knit-blazer-P186133&amp;sdReferer=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bananarepublic.ca%2Fproducts%2Fsuits-blazers-mens-sale-C1014860.jsp&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; this herringbone grey blazer from Banana Republic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for $40. Click the link and see the regular price...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt; 3. It has to be really versatile.&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything black, white, grey, or navy blue is generally quite versatile. Unless you&#39;ve got piles of cash, your focus should be building a wardrobe, not singular outfits. I got the three long sleeve tees in the cover photo for this post for $12 each.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless an item meets all three of those criteria, I&#39;m not buying it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Get a shirt collar extender&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of the 10 shirts I own, only 2 of them fit my neck. If I wore a tie with the other 8, they squeezed my neck so hard I had to sacrifice 70% of my brain&#39;s daily oxygen supply. Then I found out about collar extenders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/collar.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;I got these ones for $15 at Moore&#39;s. You can get others online for about $3 each.&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For $15, my possible tie-shirt combination&#39;s went from &lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; (2 shirts X 10 ties) to &lt;strong&gt;100&lt;/strong&gt; (10 shirts X 10 ties)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Add some accents. &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;(to your outfits, not your speech)&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One really easy, inexpensive way to do this is to buy coloured shoelaces. I got 4 pairs for about $15 at Winners. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Moneysworth-Best-Basics-Dress-Coloured/dp/B00GTLAKZ4/ref=pd_sim_468_3?ie=UTF8&amp;refRID=03V2JC2Z03AWPJ5V03ZH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;You can buy the same ones on Amazon for $10.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; By doing this, you can turn one pair of shoes into 4 or 5 variations, instantly.&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Now Let&#39;s do the math &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Herringbone Blazer = $40 &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;+&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;White, Black, &amp; Grey Long Sleeve Tee&#39;s = $36 ($12 Each)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;+&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Tapered Old Jeans = $0 if you D.I.Y. &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;+&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Collar Extender = $3 off Amazon&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;+&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Coloured Shoelaces = $10 off Amazon&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;=&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt; $89 &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you really want to improve your wardrobe, and avoid breaking the bank in the process, you need to take the time to read and learn. Don&#39;t be afraid to ask advice from friends either. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Reddit&#39;s male fashion advice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; has been a huge help for me. Good luck!!!&lt;/p&gt;







































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/07/26/Improve-your-wardrobe.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/07/26/Improve-your-wardrobe.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My First Ever Vlog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve wanted to try vlogging for a few weeks now and kept running into setbacks, but I finally got one done! I even found a travelling book, which was insanely serendipitous (I swear it wasn&#39;t a set up). Check it out!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First thing is first, holy s*** I underestimated how much work this takes. I had to edit about 250 individual clips, and had the genius idea to try a new editing software for the first time. I also completely ran out of space on my mac (even after deleting everything I could possibly spare), so I had to borrow an 
external hard drive before I could finish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My parents are also going to hate me for walking along the edge of the bridge again, but I swear it&#39;s not as sketchy as it looks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;410&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xrTEwqirtHU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my very first vlog, I&#39;m pleased with the result. I definitely learned a lot in the process, and I now know not to record 400 clips... I also now know what the sound quality is like on the first gen go pro, and I know how user friendly Adobe Premiere Pro is &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;NOT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I also know that I need to do a better job of telling a story as I go, instead of just slapping random clips together. For example, when Nico and I went to the library I didn&#39;t really explain what we were doing. For anyone wondering, we were working on the matchup schedule for this week&#39;s Lawn Summer Nights. Week 2 spectator tickets have already sold out, so stay tuned for week 3 tickets!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure how often I will be vlogging, as it requires a totally different skill set and work load than just writing blog material. I definitely think it&#39;s a cool concept and will be making some more for sure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  Feedback is very much appreciated, so please send me a message on facebook or leave comments on the youtube video, if you have any thoughts or ideas for me!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/07/09/First-Vlog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/07/09/First-Vlog.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Night of Lawn Summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This past Thursday, I attended the first night of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.982566371806116.1073741886.343801065682653&amp;type=3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lawn Summer Nights Halifax&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; for 2015, and had a blast! Click &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.982566371806116.1073741886.343801065682653&amp;type=3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HERE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for photos! I was so happy to see some familiar faces, and also had the pleasure of meeting some awesome new friends. In the middle of the event, there was a moment, during which three friends of mine fell within my direct line of vision, and I thought to myself, “Those are three fantastic people”. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These three people have all inspired me, and I am sure they inspire many others – probably more than they realize. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/thumbs.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; My friend Stefan speaking before bowling.&lt;br&gt; Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/melhadtea/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Mel Hattie&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;. All Lawn Summer Nights photos in this post were taken by &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/melhadtea/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Mel!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first of these three special people, is my close friend, Stefan Strecko. Stefan was born with cystic fibrosis, and spoke at both last year&#39;s and this year&#39;s events, about CF, and about what this event means to him and to others living with CF. Last year, I was impressed by Stefan&#39;s confidence on the mic. This year, I was blown away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stefan and I first became friends when we were about 12 years old, while playing our first year of peewee football together. I&#39;ll never forget the first time I found out about Stefan&#39;s CF, months after we had become friends. Stefan&#39;s mom had to tell my mom, because he was coming over for our first sleepover. I remember thinking to myself, &quot;why hasn&#39;t he said anything before?&quot;, and &quot;how the hell is he so strong?&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To this day, I have never once heard Stefan complain about the hand he&#39;s been dealt, and he has never let it define him. Stefan was a star football player in high school, a Canada Games freestyle skier, and benches over 300 lbs. He is also one of the most infectiously positive individuals I&#39;ve ever been around. As someone who tends to feel like the whole world just might end when I have a cold, I cannot say enough about my admiration for Stefan&#39;s unfathomable toughness and perseverance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stefan, you inspire me. And I thank you for teaching me to stay positive and to persevere when faced with adversity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/davenstef.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Here&#39;s a hilarious photo of Stefan and I when we were about 13&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The other two of these three people, are Mel Hattie and Emily Savage (seen in the photo below). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/guys.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Mel (left) Emily (right) &lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said before, these ladies have provided me with more inspiration than they know. Emily was responsible for bringing Lawn Summer Nights (one of the most awesome things I&#39;ve ever been involved with) to Halifax, and if I hadn&#39;t been inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/melhadtea/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Mel&#39;s blogging&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;, you wouldn&#39;t be reading this right now. Despite their insane schedules, Mel and Emily always seem to find time to help others, donning their big, beautiful smiles in the process. They also seem to always be travelling to awesome places, which tells me I need to stop making excuses for why I can&#39;t travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know gender should be irrelevant, but there&#39;s just something extra-awesome about female role models! Expect big things from these two!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/fam.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Brayden and I with our grandparents&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will cap this post off with a triple-whammy of inspiration. In the photo above, from left to right, you&#39;ll see my brother Brayden, My grandfather &quot;Red&quot;, my lovely grandmother Mary, and myself. This photo was taken at my grandparents&#39; cottage, while celebrating their 62nd anniversary. We&#39;re holding the gift that Brayden and I gave to them; custom labeled cider bottles, designed by Brayden, with photographs from when they were about our age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/mary.png&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/red.png&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My grandparents have always inspired me. Again, probably more than they know. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for my brother, I want to start by congratulating him on being accepted to McGill University! So proud of you, Dude. Sometimes it can be a tough pill to swallow, but he has always been the brain. A few years ago, after being shocked by his knowledge on random subjects, I asked him how he had come to know so much.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt; His response:&lt;/strong&gt; &quot;You know when you used to ask me to come outside and play hockey, but I would stay inside &#39;like a loser&#39; and read books? Yeah, I was learning shit!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well said Brother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive media-center hover-cursor&quot; src=&quot;/img/bruh.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; data-action=&quot;zoom&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;a photo of brayden and I (probably around &#39;98 or &#39;99), again at our grandparents&#39; cottage.&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brayden has taught me a lot about the importance of reading, learning, growing, and, most importantly, about being a kind person. I am no angel, and Brayden has never been shy when it comes to calling me on my bull. I thank him for holding me to such a high standard. It&#39;s been humbling to learn so much from my little brother, who is 4 years younger than me, but I am beyond grateful for all that he&#39;s taught me. Again, expect big things from this one...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to these people, and to the many others, who have inspired me and challenged me to become a better person, whether intentionally or simply by setting the right example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h4&gt; Be sure to check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/melhadtea/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Mel&#39;s Instagram Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.982566371806116.1073741886.343801065682653&amp;type=3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Her Album from Lawn Summer Nights!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
































		



















	










 
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 09:55:44 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/07/05/Lawn-Summer-Nights.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://daveculligan.ca/jekyll/update/2015/07/05/Lawn-Summer-Nights.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
